(Penny's dad (Wyatt):)that knows how to use a napkin.
(Penny:)So not funny, Dad.
(Wyatt:)Let me tell you about this one
genius she was going out with,
this-this
fella Donnie.
(Penny:)Oh, will you please let it go?
(Wyatt:)Donnie was gonna make millions
turning farm waste
(Wyatt:)into biofuel and selling it
to the government.
(Leonard:)A lot of people are doing that.
(Penny:)Oh, see?
(Wyatt:)Yeah, but all Donnie did was mix
pig poop with a little water
(Wyatt:)and pump it
into his mom's Camry.
(Penny:)Yeah, that's great.
(Penny:)It's a funny story. Moving on.
(Wyatt:)And Donnie was a rocket
scientist compared to that boy
(Wyatt:)who wanted to get beer pong
into the Olympics.
(Wyatt:)What was his
name, sweetheart?
(Penny:)Curtis, and I'm pretty sure
he was joking.
(Wyatt:)I don't know.
(Wyatt:)That petition
looked real to me.
(Penny:)Yeah, okay, I think this ends
(Penny:)the ex-boyfriend portion
of our evening.
(Wyatt:)Well, I'm just glad you finally
found yourself a keeper.
(Leonard:)Thanks, Wyatt.
(Leonard:)I'm a keeper.
(Wyatt:)Leonard, you want to come in
for a nightcap?
(Penny:)Oh, gee, Dad,
he'd love to,
(Penny:)but Leonard has to work
in the morning.
(Leonard:)Maybe I could
go in a little late.
(Penny:)No, no, no, you can't.